<note>
	<author>Napoleon Hill</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Whatever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Steve Jobs</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Your time is limited, so don't waste it living someone else's life.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Carl Bard</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Though no one can go back and make a brand new start, anyone can start from now and make a brand new ending.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>When the past calls, let it go to voicemail, believe me, it has nothing new to say.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Rule #1 of life. Do what makes YOU happy.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Walk away from anything or anyone who takes away from your joy. Life is too short to put up with fools.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknwon</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Love what you have. Need what you want. Accept what you receive. Give what you can. Always remember, what goes around, comes around…</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Just remember there is someone out there that is more than happy with less than what you have.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The biggest failure you can have in life is making the mistake of never trying at all.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Life has two rules: #1 Never quit #2 Always remember rule # 1.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>No one is going to hand me success. I must go out & get it myself. That's why I'm here. To dominate. To conquer. Both the world, and myself.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Wayne Dyer</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Be miserable. Or motivate yourself. Whatever has to be done, it's always your choice.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Albert Einstein</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Robert Frost</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Two roads diverged in a wood, and I took the one less traveled by, and that has made all the difference.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Jeffrey Bezos</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The common question that gets asked in business is, ‘why?' That's a good question, but an equally valid question is, ‘why not?'</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Wayne Gretzky</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>You miss 100% of the shots you don't take.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Michael Jordan</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>I've missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I've lost almost 300 games. 26 times I've been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I've failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Babe Ruth</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Every strike brings me closer to the next home run.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>W. Clement Stone</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Definiteness of purpose is the starting point of all achievement.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>John Lennon</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Earl Nightingale</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>We become what we think about.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Mark Twain</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do, so throw off the bowlines, sail away from safe harbor, catch the trade winds in your sails.  Explore, Dream, Discover.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>John Maxwell</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Life is 10% what happens to me and 90% of how I react to it.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Tony Robbins</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>If you do what you've always done, you'll get what you've always gotten.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Buddha</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The mind is everything. What you think you become.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Chinese Proverb</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Socrates</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>An unexamined life is not worth living.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Woody Allen</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Eighty percent of success is showing up.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Napoleon Hill</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Don't wait. The time will never be just right.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Vince Lombardi</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Winning isn't everything, but wanting to win is.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Stephen Covey</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Pablo Picasso</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Every child is an artist.  The problem is how to remain an artist once he grows up.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Christopher Columbus</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>You can never cross the ocean until you have the courage to lose sight of the shore.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Maya Angelou</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Jim Rohn</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Either you run the day, or the day runs you.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Henry Ford</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Whether you think you can or you think you can't, you're right.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Mark Twain</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The two most important days in your life are the day you are born and the day you find out why.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Johann Wolfgang von Goethe</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Whatever you can do, or dream you can, begin it.  Boldness has genius, power and magic in it.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Frank Sinatra</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The best revenge is massive success.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Zig Ziglar</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>People often say that motivation doesn't last. Well, neither does bathing.  That's why we recommend it daily.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Pablo Picasso</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Inspiration exists, but it must find you working.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Vincent Van Gogh</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>If you hear a voice within you say you cannot paint, then by all means paint and that voice will be silenced.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Aristotle</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>There is only one way to avoid criticism: do nothing, say nothing, and be nothing.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Henry Ford</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Obstacles are those frightful things you see when you take your eyes off the goal.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Ralph Waldo Emerson</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Henry David Thoreau</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Go confidently in the direction of your dreams.  Live the life you have imagined.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Erma Bombeck</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>When I stand before God at the end of my life, I would hope that I would not have a single bit of talent left and could say, I used everything you gave me.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Brian Tracy</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Successful people are always looking for opportunities to help others.  Unsuccessful people are always asking, What's in it for me?</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Ancient Indian Proverb</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Certain things catch your eye, but pursue only those that capture the heart.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Theodore Roosevelt</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Believe you can and you're halfway there.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>George Addair</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Everything you've ever wanted is on the other side of fear.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Plato</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>We can easily forgive a child who is afraid of the dark; the real tragedy of life is when men are afraid of the light.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Christopher Reeve</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Once you choose hope, anything's possible.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Arthur Ashe</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Start where you are. Use what you have.  Do what you can.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>John Lennon</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>When I was 5 years old, my mother always told me that happiness was the key to life.  When I went to school, they asked me what I wanted to be when I grew up.  I wrote down ‘happy'.  They told me I didn't understand the assignment, and I told them they didn't understand life.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Japanese Proverb</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Fall seven times and stand up eight.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Helen Keller</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>When one door of happiness closes, another opens, but often we look so long at the closed door that we do not see the one that has been opened for us.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Confucious</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Everything has beauty, but not everyone can see.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Lao Tzu</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>When I let go of what I am, I become what I might be.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Dalai Lama</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Happiness is not something readymade.  It comes from your own actions.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Arthur C. Clarke</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The only way of finding the limits of the possible is by going beyond them into the impossible.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Aristotle</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>First, have a definite, clear practical ideal; a goal, an objective. Second, have the necessary means to achieve your ends; wisdom, money, materials, and methods. Third, adjust all your means to that end.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Latin Proverb</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>If the wind will not serve, take to the oars.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>You can't fall if you don't climb.  But there's no joy in living your whole life on the ground.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Vincent Van Gogh</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Whoever loves much, performs much, and can accomplish much, and what is done in love is done well.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Les Brown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Joshua J. Marine</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Walt Disney</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Benjamin Franklin</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>I didn't fail the test. I just found 100 ways to do it wrong.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Bill Cosby</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>In order to succeed, your desire for success should be greater than your fear of failure.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Albert Einstein</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new.</quote>
</note>



<note>
	<author>Chinese Proverb</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The person who says it cannot be done should not interrupt the person who is doing it.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Roger Staubach</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>There are no traffic jams along the extra mile.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>George Eliot</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>It is never too late to be what you might have been.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Oprah Winfrey</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>You become what you believe.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Vincent van Gogh</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>I would rather die of passion than of boredom.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>A truly rich man is one whose children run into his arms when his hands are empty.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Ann Landers</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>It is not what you do for your children, but what you have taught them to do for themselves, that will make them successful human beings.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Farrah Gray</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Build your own dreams, or someone else will hire you to build theirs.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Frank Zappa</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Without deviation from the norm, progress is not possible.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Sir Claus Moser</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Education costs money.  But then so does ignorance.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>H. Jackson Brown, Jr.</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Remember that the happiest people are not those getting more, but those giving more.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Confucius</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>H. Jackson Brown, Jr.</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Let the refining and improving of your own life keep you so busy that you have little time to criticize others.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Dalai Lama</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Remember that not getting what you want is sometimes a wonderful stroke of luck.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Maya Angelou</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>You can't use up creativity.  The more you use, the more you have.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Martin Luther King Jr.</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Our lives begin to end the day we become silent about things that matter.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Teddy Roosevelt</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Do what you can, where you are, with what you have.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Alice Walker</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The most common way people give up their power is by thinking they don't have any.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Gloria Steinem</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Dreaming, after all, is a form of planning.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Mae Jemison</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>It's your place in the world; it's your life. Go on and do all you can with it, and make it the life you want to live.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Beverly Sills</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>You may be disappointed if you fail, but you are doomed if you don't try.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Eleanor Roosevelt</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Remember no one can make you feel inferior without your consent.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Grandma Moses</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Life is what we make it, always has been, always will be.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Ayn Rand</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The question isn't who is going to let me; it's who is going to stop me.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Abraham Lincoln</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>It's not the years in your life that count. It's the life in your years.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Benjamin Franklin</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Audrey Hepburn</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Nothing is impossible, the word itself says, I'm possible!</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Steve Jobs</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The only way to do great work is to love what you do.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Zig Ziglar</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>If you can dream it, you can achieve it.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Just know, when you truly want success, you'll never give up on it. No matter how bad the situation may get.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Les Brown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Accept responsibility for your life. Know that it is you who will get you where you want to go, no one else.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>I don't regret the things I've done, I regret the things I didn't do when I had the chance.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Joshua J. Marine</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful.</quote>
</note>


<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Its hard to wait around for something you know might never happen; but its harder to give up when you know its everything you want.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>One of the most important keys to Success is having the discipline to do what you know you should do, even when you dont feel like doing it.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Good things come to those who wait… greater things come to those who get off their ass and do anything to make it happen.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Denis Waitley</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Happiness cannot be traveled to, owned, earned, or worn. It is the spiritual experience of living every minute with love, grace & gratitude.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Bill Cosby</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>In order to succeed, your desire for success should be greater than your fear of failure.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Go where you are celebrated  not tolerated. If they can't see the real value of you, it's time for a new start.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Dont be afraid to stand for what you believe in, even if that means standing alone..</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Frank Sinatra</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The best revenge is massive success.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Forget all the reasons it won't work and believe the one reason that it will.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Albert Einstein</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>I am thankful for all of those who said NO to me. Its because of them I'm doing it myself.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Steve Jobs</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The only way to do great work is to love what you do. If you haven't found it yet, keep looking. Don't settle.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Life is short, live it. Love is rare, grab it. Anger is bad, dump it. Fear is awful, face it. Memories are sweet, cherish it.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>When you say It's hard, it actually means I'm not strong enough to fight for it. Stop saying its hard. Think positive!</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Life is like photography. You need the negatives to develop.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Jack Canfield</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Don't worry about failures, worry about the chances you miss when you don't even try.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The pain you feel today is the strength you feel tomorrow. For every challenge encountered there is opportunity for growth.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Farrah Gray</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Build your own dreams, or someone else will hire you to build theirs.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Joel Brown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>The only thing that stands between you and your dream is the will to try and the belief that it is actually possible.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Self confidence is the most attractive quality a person can have. how can anyone see how awesome you are if you can't see it yourself?</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>We learn something from everyone who passes through our lives.. Some lessons are painful, some are painless.. but, all are priceless.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Being happy doesn't mean that everything is perfect. it means that you've decided to look beyond the imperfections.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Larry Winget</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Nobody ever wrote down a plan to be broke, fat, lazy, or stupid. Those things are what happen when you don't have a plan.</quote>
</note>

<note>
	<author>Unknown</author>
	<tag></tag>
	<quote>Three things you cannot recover in life: the WORD after it's said, the MOMENT after it's missed and the TIME after it's gone. Be Careful!</quote>
</note>